(Leonard:)All I'm saying is, if they
took all the money they spent
(Leonard:)trying to make
a decent Hulk movie,
(Leonard:)they could probably
just make an actual Hulk.
(Sheldon:)That is apt and amusing.
(Sheldon:)I think I shall share that
(Sheldon:)with Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Sheldon:)She'll appreciate
the witticism.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)It'll also help improve her
initial impression of you.
(Leonard:)So what's going on with you two?
(Sheldon:)Well, the status is
as it always was.
(Sheldon:)She's a girl. She's a friend.
(Sheldon:)She is not my--
(Sheldon:)please forgive me
for doing this--
"girlfriend."
(Leonard:)Right, right.
(Leonard:)So you're still just
texting and emailing?
(Leonard:)You don't feel any need
to hang out with her, you know--
(Leonard:)be in the same room?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you are
my best friend.
(Sheldon:)I've known you
for seven years,
(Sheldon:)and I can barely tolerate
sitting on the couch with you.
(Sheldon:)Imagine my attitude regarding
prolonged physical proximity
(Sheldon:)to Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Leonard:)Got it.